### Privacy Policy

last update date: 18 February, 2022

This Privacy Policy explains RITS Browser’s policy regarding the privacy of information supplied by users or collected by us from users of RITS Browser. We are committed to protecting your privacy. This Policy may change over time as we modify or expand our service; we suggest that you check back from time to time in order to understand how we treat your information. The RITS Browser contain links to other sites that are not under our control. These web sites have their own policies regarding privacy. You should review those policies before visiting the web sites. We have no responsibility for linked web sites, and we provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

### 1\. What Information is Being Collected

##### Manually provided information

RITS Browser collects certain information from and about its users. You may provide your personal information to us, such as your phone and email addresses, when you access certain Services offered via the RITS Browser, for instance, when you create an account on RITS Browser Services (including login with other third party accounts). It is your choice whether to send this personal information to us. We may contact wit you via email, sms or social media to inform you about our upcoming services/product or any upgrade is going on. If you give us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and email address, as well as any other content included in the email, in order to send you a reply. When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional information provided by you to us as part of the surveys. You may also provide other types of Information to us voluntarily if you contact us via e-mail requesting support from RITS Browser. It is your choice whether to send such personal information to us. In addition, when you use RITS Browser Services, RITS Browser will have access to information you post to RITS Browser including, but not limited to, threads and comments you post in forums. [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

### 2\. Automatically collected information

To make RITS Browser Services more useful to you, we may collect information from you, including but not limited to: 1. Software information, such as version, distribution, system version and application list. 2. Hardware information, such as IMEI, MAC address of your device, model info, manufacturer. 3. Information regarding your usage, such as browser type, language preference, time and time zone, errors and reports, buttons clicked, settings, typing in the URL bar. 4. Network information: IP address, network carrier, rough location according to the IP address or Wi-Fi connected by / around you, referring site, and speed of each visitor request. 5. Location of your device or computer (if you grant permission). When you are visiting RITS Browser webite, we also use cookies (and similar technologies) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and what you search and view. Cookies etc. are computer files that are saved to your device and which may store information about you, your device, and your browser and that may be used to transmit that information to us. For example, cookies are used to identify your device and record the visit so that the RITS Browser website services can allow you access to your account without requiring you to re-enter the information.  
When you are using RITS Browser : you may choose to delete cookies or other tracking mechanisms on your browser anytime you want through your browser’s settings. You may also choose to have non-essential cookies (and similar technologies) not used by us when you access and use RITS Browser Services by amending your settings at –your browser’s settings (if applicable). RITS Browser also write cookies to give you the customize services: such as localize content.

### 3\. Information from other sources

We may obtain information about you from business partners, contractors, and other third parties and add it to our account information or other information we have collected. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via RITS Browser Services in order to improve RITS Browser Services. We may allow users to log in with their Facebook or Google log in information. Under these circumstances and if you have given your consent, we may have access to your profile information stored on the Facebook and/or Google applications (as applicable), including name, email address, picture, gender, age-range, birthday, friends list, marital status and employment history, and in addition in relation to Facebook, education history and religion.

### 4\. Registration data

When you signup with us we collect your personal information to verify and protect your account with RITS Browser. It require so that we can provide you all the personalize benifits to you. Such as: Verify your account, giving you reward videos, your order detail, available earned points etc.

### 5\. Information accuracy

When you provide personal information to us, you agree to provide accurate information only, and agree that we may assume its accuracy and rely on it. If we provide means for you to update your information, you agree to update the information to keep it accurate.

### 6\. Use of Data

RITS Browser uses the collected data for various purposes:* a. To provide and maintain the Service
* b. To notify you about changes to our Service
* c. To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
* d. To provide customer care and support
* e. To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
* f. To monitor the usage of the Service
* g. To detect, prevent and address technical issues

### 7\. Disclosure of Data

##### Legal Requirements

RITS Browser may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:* a. To comply with a legal obligation
* b. To protect and defend the rights or property of RITS Browser
* c. To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* d. To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
* e. To protect against legal liability

### 8\. Service Provider

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analysing how our Service is used. These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### 9\. Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyse the use of our Service.

### i) Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. You may opt-out of certain Google Analytics features through your mobile device settings, such as your device advertising settings or by following the instructions  
provided by Google in their Privacy Policy: [www.policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)  
For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [www.policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

### ii) Firebase

Firebase is analytics service provided by Google Inc. You may opt-out of certain Firebase features through your mobile device settings, such as your device advertising settings or by following the instructions provided by Google in their Privacy Policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en We also encourage you to review the Google's policy for safeguarding your data: https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245. For more information on what type of information Firebase collects, please visit please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en

### 10\. The Use of That Information

We may use your information to provide personalized content and services. Any account information you supply will be used only to process requested commerce transaction or to contact you regarding a specific inquiry or transaction.

### 11\. Third Party Distribution

RITS Browser will not wilfully disclose any individually identifiable information about its users to any third party without first receiving that user’s permission.

### 12\. Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, such as firewalls and authentication protection. All data are transmitted over secure Internet connections using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption technology. All of your personal information including your credit card information is stored in an unreadable, encrypted format at all times. This web site, and more importantly all user information, is further protected by a multilayer firewall based security system.

### 13\. Changes to this privacy policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service or a notification on our app, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

### 14\. Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us: • By email: [\[email protected\]](https://ritsbrowser.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

### 15\. Delete Account data

If you want to delete your account data, please contact us: By email: [\[email protected\]](https://ritsbrowser.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection), we will delete your account and all data stored in our system (If you want to remove your email from our email list you have to unsubscribe separately). We keep all registration data of suspended accounts so that they can not register with us again.
